Damn, this bastard's here.
Got here faster than me.
Brother Liu.
Don't hurt yourself.
You better worry about yourselves.
None of you are leaving today.
Doctor!
What happened?
The patient had a sudden heart attack.
Their condition was critical.
We did everything we could.
But...
Ma'am.
My condolences.
He was perfectly fine at noon.
He was still cooking in the kitchen.
How could he just be gone like that?
Ma'am.
This is a little something from our colleagues.
Please accept it.
Officer.
I just want to ask you one thing.
Can you catch those scammers?
Rest assured, ma'am.
I promise you,
even if they flee to the ends of the earth,
the police
will definitely bring them to justice.
Shanshan
Everyone,
the Huang Shanshan case has become a major public issue.
The social impact has been extremely severe.
Our superiors have given us strict orders.
Targeting the rampant local telecom fraud,
we must solve the case within a month.
Captain Sun, we guarantee to complete the mission.
Let's get to work.
Interrogate the suspects we arrested last time.
Investigate all possible leads.
We must act quickly
to catch this gang of scammers.
Brother Liu!
Boss Liu!
Is there some kind of misunderstanding here?
Bro Snake, what does this mean?
Everything was fine,
why are you tying me up?
Beat him!
Speak!
Did you bring the cops here?
Boss Liu!
I'm innocent!
I don't know why the cops showed up!
Keep lying.
You might fool others,
but you can't fool me!
I've been in this business for years.
Both times things went south, it was with you!
This company has had trouble since you arrived.
If you're not the mole, who is?
That's not fair to say.
Our deal was almost done.
You were the one rushing to withdraw the cash.
That's why the cops locked onto us!
I had just left,
and the cops showed up!
How can you blame me for that?
Then it must be...
Gu Yan!
That's right!
He ran a rental pig-butchering scam recently.
Not only did he not lay low,
he also provoked the cops!
That's how we got targeted!
Gu Yan...
And Boss Liu,
we've been mass-recruiting college students lately.
The police tech department definitely noticed us.
The cops definitely won't let us off the hook.
Right, Boss Liu?
I'm truly innocent!
Right my ass!
This place is so well hidden,
could the cops even find it?
You won't speak, huh?
Beat him!
You hit me?
Are you out of your mind?
He's already suffered enough, and you're still hitting him?
You're exactly who I want to hit!
Playing the good guy, huh?
Is it funny?
I didn't laugh.
Bro Snake.
Are we really doing this?
Li Wen is new.
If he dies, he dies.
But you're a veteran.
If you die,
it would break my heart.
Wait, Bro Snake.
Let's talk this out.
There must be a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding, huh?
Then tell me...
...what's the real story...
...behind this Li Wen?
How should I know?
You told me to find a tech-savvy programmer.
I just happened to run into this clueless kid.
And I checked him out, too.
He seemed totally clean.
"Just happened to"?
Looks premeditated to me.
No.
I really didn't know!
And didn't you guys check him too?
He's just a regular working programmer!
Old Gu.
My live-streaming and gambling teams got busted.
I accepted that.
Now even the telecom and tech teams...
...have gone down too.
I'm ready to kill someone right now.
Beat him.
Kill me if you have the guts.
Make it quick.
Bro Snake.
What's going on?
He's sick.
Sick?
With what?
He's sick in the head.
Never mind that.
Pretty boy.
Stop holding out.
Old Gu spilled everything.
You're an undercover sent by the cops.
Don't mention cops to me.
I hate cops more than anything in my life.
Still won't talk, huh?
A keyboard jockey.
You make a living with your hands, right?
What are you doing?
Dodging?
Think you can dodge this?
Bro Snake,
these two definitely got their stories straight.
Give me another half day.
Not even half a day.
I'll definitely make them talk.
Are you
sure they're guilty?
They definitely are!
Who else could it be?
How long have you been beating them?
About an hour and a half, I guess.
Then let me ask you,
if I beat you for this long,
would you talk?
I'd confess.
Useless.
That's enough.
Let him out.
Bro Snake,
you're really just letting him go?
There's no point in holding out anymore.
You might as well just confess.
It was Old Liu.
That 500,000,
he forced me to transfer it to him secretly.
Bullshit!
How dare you pin this on me!
I'll kill you!
You, keep talking.
If I didn't transfer it to him,
he wouldn't let me join the group.
Now that the group got busted,
he wants me to take the fall.
Bro Snake,
don't listen to his bullshit.
He was the one who tempted me!
He said we could split the 500,000 thirty-seventy.
I wasn't even a regular employee back then.
If you hadn't forced me,
how would I have the guts to pull these tricks?
Bro Snake, you can't believe him!
Old Liu,
you have no real skills at all.
All you do is frame people.
Bro Snake,
he saw that my hand was useful,
so he crippled my hand!
Look at what he's really up to!
Shut up!
Enough.
Our entire call center just got busted.
This is exactly when we need people.
You crippled his hand,
so how am I supposed to use him?
Bro Snake...
If we don't meet our quota,
how do we answer to Sir?
Bro Snake,
trust my intuition.
What intuition?
What kind of people did you find?
No wonder we can't succeed.
They're all trash.
Bro Snake,
this isn't your fault.
You're hardworking,
and you're capable.
The problem lies with the team.
Hear that?
Use your brain.
Be more careful when recruiting.
Untie him already!
Thank you, Bro Snake!